# Hamada ali

Web Developer Two Years experience Flutter Developer One Year experience

#### Address:

Cairo - Nasr city - Egypt

#### Phone:

+201150769418

#### Email:

hamadaali221133@gmail.com

### Summary

Web Developer specializing in backe end development. Experienced with all stages of the development cycle for dynamic web projects. Well-versed in numerous programming languages including HTML5, PHP OOP, JavaScript, CSS, MySQL. Strong background in project management and customer relations.

Flutter Developer specializing in developing mobile applications. Experienced in the development of mobile application projects, Well-versed in Firebase, working with REST APIs state management provider, SQFLITE.

## **Skill Highlights**

- Dart Flutter
- HTML&CSS
- Javascript&Jquery&Bootstra
- PHP&OOP&PDO&MYSQL
- Laraval5
- Wordpress

### **Experience**

php Wordpress Developer - 06/2016 to 04/2017 techVillgeco company PHP Laravel Developer - 01/2018 to 05/2019

#### **Matrix Couds company**

- maintain optimal workflow.
- Complete detailed programming and development tasks for front end public and internal websites as well as challenging back-end server code.
- Carry out quality assurance tests to discover errors and optimize usability.

#### Dart Flutter Developer - 06/2019 to 02/2021

FreeLancer, Work from home

- I uploaded two applications to the Play Store.
- maintain optimal workflow.
- Carry out quality assurance tests to discover errors and optimize usability.
- I uploaded two applications to the Play Store.

### **Education**

Bachelor of Science: Computer Information Systems - 2016 Graduate from High Institute for Computer Information s

# My previous work

#### **Flutter App:**

https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.maojod.maojod\_app

https://drive.google.com/file/d/1UgfRaZvj7KcxJbaRI0fNLBmw\_HV8oyEN/view?usp=sharing

https://drive.google.com/file/d/13tjBY\_2R4vARseHxt-jWsvdbw-hIp8FM/view?usp=sharing

https://file.fm/u/qdy2cpv4

#### **Web Sites:**

findfamily.net/trufaco findfamily.net/maogod/gardensdiar.com tasahel.net gamma-international.com matrixclouds.com elkasrawyauto.com matrixtranslation.com server-egy.com findfamily.net/cloud/ pf-uae.com callforatrip.com

### Languages

English – C2 Arabic – A1